{
    "subject": "resource/Joey_Molland",
    "predicate": "ontology/associatedBand",
    "object": "resource/Badfinger",
    "human_readable": "Joey Molland was associated with Badfinger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.824160099029541,
            "question": "Did Joey Molland write any songs for Badfinger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6466615200042725,
            "question": "What band was Joey Molland associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.578533947467804,
            "question": "Where was Badfinger from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5565221905708313,
            "question": "Who is Joey Molland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44837963581085205,
            "question": "Was Joey Molland a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32770007848739624,
            "question": "What are some notable achievements of Badfinger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3126786947250366,
            "question": "When was Badfinger most active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19989648461341858,
            "question": "What genre of music did Badfinger play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1997944712638855,
            "question": "Is Badfinger a rock band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18045465648174286,
            "question": "Name some popular songs by Badfinger."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joey Molland was associated with Badfinger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8543_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Badfinger a rock band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8543_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music did Badfinger play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8543_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Badfinger most active?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8543_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8543_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Joey Molland's association with the band Badfinger, supporting the statement that he was indeed associated with the band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}